[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Mikoy, your dad Mario is missing?
He's looking for Chiara on his own.
I have a hunch.
He may have seen something or followed someone.
You're the reason why I lost my family.
Sean has been talking to someone suspicious.
There's a new character in Chiara and Mikoy's lives.
We need to investigate this Vicky.
I can't bear to see you die.
You and Aunt Tess have been good to me,
so I'm here to help you.
Mario.
The car keys.
I need to take Chiara with me.
That's what I won't allow.
Mario, leave now before I change my mind.
My prayers have been answered.
Dad Mario, I'm here.
Dad Mario. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to. I didn't mean to.
Dad.
Mom, here.
Oh, honey, he doesn't like that one.
He says it makes him look fat.
How about this one?
He doesn't like that one either.
Because of his fair complexion, he says it makes him look like a radish.
This one.
He likes this one.
Because, look.
It's completely worn out because he uses it all the time.
Because…
This is your father's favorite.
I know that all of us here
are completely heartbroken.
There are so many questions.
So many of us want to cry.
But you all know Dad.
Every major event in our lives…
is a reason to celebrate.
You know, my child,
I never wanted you to bear this burden.
If only I could turn back time,
I wouldn't let this happen.
So from now on,
I'm here.
You, Angelito, and your mother,
that's what makes me so proud of you.
I want to think that's because of
how well we raised you.
Well, of course, Dad.
If it weren't for your and Mom's guidance,
I probably would've been picked up from who knows where.
Maybe.
And this event is no different.
And let's never ever forget
the space he holds in our hearts.
Mario.
Noodles for a long life.
But I don't think I believe
in that saying anymore.
Mario, that's so unfair.
You left us too soon.
To the best barangay captain we ever had.
And to the fair-skinned womanizer from Albay and Cebu.
Mario.
To our idol, whom we all look up to.
The guide who serves as a light for the drunkards.
And for those who are down in the dumps.
To my second father.
A father who, even though we weren't related by blood,
never abandoned me.
A father who became more of a father to me than my own father.
Cheers to Mario.
I'll miss all your jokes, Dad.
No one should know, not even your own mother.
You mean,
-I'd be lying to my mom. -You wouldn't be lying.
There's just something you didn't tell her.
I'll miss how you always found a way whenever
life got too heavy.
Most of all…
I'll miss having someone I knew would always be there for me,
no matter what happens in life.
Thank you for your love, Mario.
For loving us more than we could ever ask for.
For a love so pure that it reaches all the way to heaven.
A love that never asked for anything in return.
A love that never complained.
A love that is unconditional.
Don't worry, my love.
I'll take care of the children.
Rest now, my love.
We'll see each other again. Just wait for me.
Oh, Mom.
To Dad Mario.
To the father of all of you.
To the man I love.
Always leaving us behind.
Always leaving.
NORBERTO S. RUIZ GENERAL
Say hi to our friends for me up there.
Our buddy is happy up there now.
You should've seen it.
Everyone here had so much to say about you, Dad.
Everyone from around here.
It was all good.
There weren't any haters.
I'll miss you, Dad.
This is my promise to you, Dad.
I'll make everyone who did this to you pay.
Child.
Mama, Papa.
Chiara.
Yes, what happened, child?
What happened was,
just the other day, we were locked up.
Then suddenly, they put us on our private plane,
and now we're here, in Prague.
We thought it was the end for both of us.
But why are we here, child?
Viktor and Donabel escaped!
How did that happen?
They were our last hope
to pin out Chiara.
And they still managed to escape!
Sir,
that's not even the bad news yet.
We have reason to believe
that they've already left the country.
What?
Why, my dear?
She's the new leader of the Concordat.
What are you doing here?
Just because you married an foreigner,
you think you're better than everyone?
I don't care about your plans for your life.
Don't get near my daughter
and try to wash her brain.
Wash her brain?
Brainwash, duh. You slowpoke.
Mama, no one's being brainwashed here.
This is my own decision.
And Mama Yaya will be part of my plans moving forward.
The Concordat always manages to slip through our fingers.
Is this agency even useful anymore?
Maybe you've forgotten?
She killed
Mario Pinagpala,
who was Mikoy's father!
You're making the wrong decision.
Didn't you say
you wanted a quiet life,
and that you loved Mikoy so much?
Didn't you two already plan a life together?
What happened?
Stop pretending.
Let's face it.
We all know there's really no future for Mikoy and me.
I can't escape who I really am.
NORBERTO S. RUIZ GENERAL
And you were the one who killed him?
He wasn't supposed to be there.
He shouldn't have gotten involved.
He shouldn't have gotten caught up in this.
How could you do that, child?
What did Mikoy say?
How did you explain what happened to him?
Well, I don't need to explain anymore
because we don't need to see each other anymore.
that if we keep forcing this relationship,
more people will get caught in the crossfire.
More family members
or innocent lives could be lost.
Mikoy and I are over.
The illusion that I could still have a happy and normal life is over.
Our assumption is that Chiara is no longer in the country.
So there's nothing we can do?
Where is she now?
She has a lot of allies there, so she's safe.
That's also where Viktor and Donabel got their private jet.
I have to accept the fact that I'm a Valtrovi,
that this is my life,
and that I'll die as a true mafia.
And if he ever threatens my position,
or derails any of my plans,
I'll send him to where his father is now.
Don't we have connections in Prague?
With the Czech authorities?
Well, yes, but…
when it comes to sharing information,
or getting their cooperation to apprehend Chiara,
I doubt it very much.
And with their influence,
I doubt there's much we can do to hold them accountable.
So that's it?
We're not going to do anything?
It doesn't matter whether you can do something or not.
I made a promise
that I'll make everyone who did this to Dad pay,
and that's what I'll do.
All I ask, Sir Norberto,
is please stay out of my way.
Looks like Donabel and Viktor don't like me.
Don't mind them. I'm sure they'll come around.
If you hadn't decided to become the Concordat,
they'd still be in prison right now.
By the way, where's Rahmboy?
He stayed behind in the Philippines,
to do some mop-up operations.
And to make sure everything is clean.
Norberto's agency won't bother us anymore.
They have no reason to investigate us anymore.
I don't think Mikoy will be a problem.
Maybe he can convince these people
and turn everyone against us.
Mikoy.
Mikoy, where are you going?
If I'm not mistaken,
I am no longer a police asset of this agency.
You don't get to run my life anymore.
I understand what you're feeling.
Really?
You have no idea
what I'm going through.
Our top priority is how to control the Concordat.
What about you? What will you do?
I will go back to the Philippines.
To make sure that Rahmboy cleared all the mess.
There’s still someone who’s in my way in leading the Concordat.
Who?
If you’re going to kill me, Chiara, or anyone else,
the hurt that you are feeling now won’t go away.
The day that you killed my father.
What do you want?
We are the agency that can bend rules for the sake of justice.